barclayscenter.com 2019-06-16

# Privacy Policy | Barclays Center

At Barclays Center we understand that privacy is an important issue for visitors to our websites and users of our services, and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes the information we collect, what we do with it and the safeguards we have in place to protect it. This Policy governs your use of this website (the “Website”), Barclays Center services, features, applications or functions offered or made available on or through the Website, or other services or applications made available by Barclays Center in which this Policy is posted (including, without limitation, mobile applications and social networking applications (e.g., Facebook) (collectively, the “Services”), as well as Barclays Center’s collection, use and disclosure of information on this Website and/or through the Services. Furthermore, this Policy applies whether you are accessing the Website and/or Services through the use of your personal computer, a mobile device or any other technology or software known today or developed in the future. Before you submit any information to the Website or Services, please read this Policy for an explanation of how we will treat your personal information. By using any part of the Website or Services and submitting your personal data, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as further outlined below in this Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not provide personal identifiable data to us. Your use of any part of the Website or Services indicates your acceptance of this Policy and of the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Policy. Please note that this Policy applies only to personal information collected on the Website or through the Services. It does not apply to any other information collected or obtained by any other means by members of the “Barclays Center Family”. For purposes of this Policy, the term “Barclays Center Family” includes, as modified and without limitation, Brooklyn Events Center, LLC, its direct and indirect parent companies and their respective affiliated entities.

As we update and expand our services, we reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes will be posted here so that you are always aware of what information is collected, how it is used and when, if ever, it is disclosed. Your continued use of the Website will signify acceptance of the terms of the new policy.

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you register for an account, use the Services or visit certain portions of the Website, you may be prompted to provide, on a voluntary basis, certain information about yourself such as: (i) name; (ii) email address; (iii) age; (iv) mailing address; (v) hobbies; (vi) sports and entertainment interests; (vii) telephone number; (viii) fax number; and (ix) viewpoints on current events. You are not required to provide any information to use our Website or Services, although certain areas may require you to have an account and will not be accessible without registration. Locations on our Website at which information may be collected include, without limitation, voluntary online surveys, promotional offerings and sweepstakes.  
We may collect location information, including general information (e.g., IP address, zip code) and more specific information (e.g., GPS-based location information from your mobile device) and use that information to deliver content and advertising based on your current location. If you access the Website or Services from a mobile device and you do not want to provide us with GPS-based location information, you can disable the GPS or other location-tracking functions on your device or the location-based features of the mobile application (if applicable).  
If you access the Website or Services through a third-party connection or log-in (e.g., through a social network), we may also collect your public user ID associated with that third-party service, and any information you have made public in connection with that service and which the third party shares with partner services pursuant to that service’s terms.  
Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. If you choose to post User Content (as described in our Terms of Service) on the Website or through the Services, such as via SNSs, on message boards, chat areas, comments, or other postings, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties.

### COOKIES

In addition to information that identifies you, we collect anonymous data about your use of the Website and Services through the use of Internet server logs and cookies, pixels, and Adobe Flash technologies. A web server log is a file where website activity is stored. A cookie is a small piece of information that a website places on your computer. We use cookies to track repeat visits to our Website and the Services. We may also use these automated technologies to collect and analyze other non-personal information related to the devices you use to access the Website and Services, such as IP address, browser types, browser language, and unique device identifier and other information about your mobile device(s).  
Please note that you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information (e.g., https://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies). You can also manage the use of Flash technologies, including cookies, with the Flash management tools available at Adobe’s website, see https://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security/privacy_policy/faq.html. Please note that by blocking any or all cookies you may not have access to certain features available through the Website or Services.  
We use third parties to assist us in serving advertisements, tracking aggregate site usage statistics, and providing content sharing services to support the Website or Services. These third parties may also use cookies and similar technologies to collect similar non-personal information about your visits to the Website and/or use of the Services. We do not control these third-party technologies and their use is governed by those parties’ privacy policies. For more information about third-party ad networks that use these technologies, and to opt-out of their collection of information, see https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

### HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

The Barclays Center Family may use your information for the following purposes:  
• For the purposes for which you provided it;  
• To send you information about your relationship or transactions with us;  
• To send you alerts or other communications via SMS messages or other media or networks;  
• To notify you about new features of the Services, discounts, special events, or products, services, and special offers;  
• To administer sweepstakes and contests;  
• To process and respond to your inquiries;  
• To contact you with information that we believe will be of interest to you;  
• To attribute content that you make available through the Website or the Services;  
• For internal research and reporting;  
• To improve the content and features of the Services or develop new Services;  
• To allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you see on the Website or the Services;  
• To enforce the legal terms that govern your use of the Website or the Services; and  
• To administer and troubleshoot the Services.

We may send you commercial email on behalf of ourselves, other members of the Barclays Center Family, and certain unaffiliated third parties that are not part of the Barclays Center Family (e.g. sites that offer discounts for certain products, sells tickets, sells Barclays Center merchandise, or advertises ticket promotions or provides fantasy games, subscription services, registration for camps and clinics, etc.) (“Partners”). You may opt-out of receiving such emails by using the opt-out mechanism included in each email.  
We may also combine information that we collect from you with information we obtain about you from other members of the Barclays Center Family or non-affiliated third parties.  
We may aggregate and/or anonymize information collected through the Website or the Services so that the information does not identify you. We may use anonymous or aggregated data for any purpose, including for research and marketing purposes, and may also share such data with third parties such as advertisers.

### WHEN WE DISCLOSE USER INFORMATION

We will not disclose personal information to non-affiliated third parties, other than the disclosures to the Barclays Center Family and Partners as described in this Policy, unless (a) it is necessary for us to render our services or conduct a legitimate business activity related to our services; or (b) you provide an appropriate consent in advance.  
We have contracted with certain unaffiliated third parties that are not part of the Barclays Center Family (“Partners”) to offer specific services and products through the Website or the Services, e.g., to offer discounts for certain products via third-party websites, sell tickets or Barclays Center merchandise, advertise ticket promotions, provide fantasy games or subscription services, conduct sweepstakes and contests, handle registration for camps and clinics, etc. We may share information we have collected from and about you with these Partners so they may send you special offers, allow you to participate in sweepstakes and contests, etc.  
We may provide access to information to select third parties to assist us in providing services or for other legitimate business purposes. For example, we may provide access to certain information to companies providing services to us, including billing, sales and marketing, market research, fulfillment, data storage, analysis and processing, and legal services. We may also provide access to third parties who assist us in providing targeted advertising. The frequency of such access depends on our business needs, and third parties who have such access may not use the information for any other purpose, including their own marketing.  
You acknowledge, consent and agree that we may access, preserve and disclose your account information and content if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (a) comply with legal process; (b) enforce our Terms of Service, Privacy Policy, or other contracts with you; © respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third parties; (d) respond to your requests for customer service; or (e) protect the rights, property or personal safety of Barclays Center, its agents and affiliates, its users and the public. We may also disclose information to law enforcement agencies in emergency circumstances, where the disclosure of such information is consistent with the types of emergency disclosures permitted or required by law.

Finally, we also reserve the right to disclose and transfer all of your information, including your personal information, to a successor company in connection with a merger, acquisition or sale of all, or components, of our business.

### CONSENT TO TRANSFER

This site is operated in the United States. If you are a resident of the European Union or other location outside the United States, please be advised that any information you provide through the Website or use of the Services will be transferred to the United States. In addition, we may transfer personal information to Singapore for certain processing operations. We have taken steps to ensure your personal information is appropriately protected and is processed only in accordance with this Policy. By using this Website or Services, you consent to this transfer and to the use of the personal information as described herein.

### OPTING OUT OF USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

If you have provided personal information on the Website or through use of the Services and later decide that you would rather not have the Barclays Center Family use such data for marketing purposes in accordance with Policy as provided herein, you can opt-out of this use at any time by: (i) going to the link provided at the bottom of any email you receive from a Barclays Center Family member and opting out of receiving information from any Barclays Center Family member; (ii) by sending us an email at [kisada@brooklynse.com](mailto:kisada@brooklynse.com); or (iii) writing us at Brooklyn Events Center, LLC, 15 MetroTech Center, 11th Floor, Brooklyn, New York 11201.

### UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION

To keep information that you provide via this website accurate, current and complete, visit your Website subscription page(s) or email [kisada@brooklynse.com](mailto:kisada@brooklynse.com) to update and/or correct any information previously provided. If a member name and password were required to access the feature, you will need to provide such information to update your registration information. If you have forgotten your password, you may obtain it by visiting the registration area and requesting that a hint be sent to you at the email address you originally provided during registration. LINKS We may include links to third party websites on the Website or the Services. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Any information you provide via those sites is subject to the Privacy Policies on those websites and is not covered by this Privacy Policy.

### SECURITY

We have implemented commercially reasonable administrative, technical, and physical security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your information. Despite our best efforts, however, no website or Internet transmission can be completely secure, and we cannot guarantee that these measures will prevent every unauthorized attempt to access, use, or disclose your information.

### YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

Beginning January 1, 2005, California Law permits visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [kisada@brooklynse.com](mailto:kisada@brooklynse.com) or write to us at Brooklyn Events Center, LLC, 15 MetroTech Center, 11th Floor, Brooklyn, New York 11201.

### INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN

Barclays Center does not seek to collect any personally identifiable information directly from children under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not submit any personally identifiable information to Barclays Center.

### CONTACTING US ABOUT THIS POLICY

Please do not hesitate to contact us with any questions, concerns, requests or comments by email at [kisada@brooklynse.com](mailto:kisada@brooklynse.com) or write us at: Brooklyn Events Center, LLC, 15 MetroTech Center, 11th Floor, Brooklyn, New York 11201.  
Effective Date: November 6, 2012

Use of this site signifies your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.
